https://edwardandrews.com/privacy-policy/

(586) 268-9600 sales@edwardandrews.com Michigan’s Tooling and Workholding Specialists 0 Items
Privacy Policy what we are agreeing to when you visit this site Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
NAVIGATION
Shop
My account
Logout
Products
Chucks / Cylinders
Kitagawa
Samchully
Contact Us
Product Search Search for:
Search
Product Tags2-Jaw 3-Jaw 4-Jaw CA Style CAT40 CAT 50 Chuck accessories Chucks Closed-Center Collet Chucks CS STYLE C Style CV Style CX Style End Mill Adapter ER Collet Grease HCHF Series HCHT Series HSF Series HST Series Hydraulic Cylinders Kitagawa Long Stroke Mega Bore MHF Series MHT Series Open-Center Power Chuck Samchully Serrated Chuck Jaws Shell Adapter SH Series Slotted snap jaws step jaws T-Nuts Tap Holder Tool Holder Bushing VDI Static vise jaws With Clearance Holes With Set Screw With Slit Z Bushing 5410 Gatewood Dr, Sterling Heights, MI 48310
